Good day!
This is Quartz News Network at six.
I am your host, [insert large word here] Seal.
During the production of QNN #6,
beings known as griefers entered our world and
destroyed many historical buildings
as well as a few commercial and housing buildings.
All of these beings have been smashed by the gods known as
"Operators" with a weapon known as "The Ban Hammer".
They also later repaired the damages as well as they could,
and have communicated the following message:
“CRSS does not tolerate any griefing or hacking.
Any player that joins with the only intention of destroying the server will be shown no mercy.
Your usernames and IPs will be banned permanently with no chance to appeal.”
While some of what they've said sounds quite confusing,
such as usernames, players and IPs,
we have chosen to recommunicate the message 1:1 so no one
infuriates the gods again.
We're excited to announce our own streaming service!
Introducing - Quartz Maximum. The optimal way to watch
Quartz Media content.
With it, you get access to all Quartz Media content directly
on the homepage. If you're overwhelmed by the amount of content
we have to offer, we provide a neat little search bar
where you can search for content.
When browsing for content, you simply hover your
cursor or finger over what you wish to play and click
or tap to start watching.
Quartz Maximum is available in two plans:
Quartz Minimum for just USD$5/month and
Quartz Maximum for USD$25/month.
Quartz Minimum has mid-roll content between ads,
Quartz Maximum is ad-free except for sponsored segments in content.
You can subscribe now at quartzmaximum.crssi.cc.
As the original Super Smelter was griefed
during The Great Grief, the original owners
will build a brand new one. It will now be located
at New Desert, and it will be much more silent.
It will remain free for everyone, so go check it out when you have the chance!
The CRSS Internet has finally launched!
There will soon be an informational website available at crssi.cc.
You will soon be able to fill out a form to register your own CRSSi website.
You can open any website on the CRSS Internet through any
modern web browser.
You can use things such as "the MCEF mod" to access the CRSS Internet
in our world, or the browsers
"FireFox, Chrome, Edge and Brave"
on the other universes.
There is a great website already available at ✨northerniiholidays.crssi.cc✨,
go check them out!
We will show you amazing news and even GREATer interviews after today's sponsor.
For years...
(or more accurately, months)
CRSS 3 Players have suffered for being unable to sprint.
This is why we invented GREAT.
With our five conveniently located stations,
You can get across everywhere (that matters) in a matter of minutes!
The best part is that it is ✨⭐100% FREE!⭐✨
So, what are you waiting for?
Use GREAT today!
GREAT is 100% free to use, however, we are not liable for
any accidents that may happen in the infrastructure.
If you intentionally use the wrong lane in the railway system,
and suffer an accident, GREAT cannot be held liable, and
will not compensate for anything that is caused.
We will fully support the well-behaving victim, though.
Yoo, wassup, gang?
Sauce Dude back... again
And... I've been- I've been playin' on this new Minecraft server
I'on even remember what it's called, it's like
ISS, or somethin'...
And I've gotta say
I'm not really a fan
of this, like, bum ***- bum *** server, okay?
It's like... It's li- [???]- There's like-
There's like two things here, alright? And everything's all green...
And it's stupid... alright-
And the website doesn't even have the right version number on it
it's like- whaareweoin-- what are we doin' here?
reoawgtjfikrewjokhnjnjnuanuttlaiujiehtgloauewjkdnoeiwapjçfoieaekwj
But...
Look at- Look at Ralsei
Look at that
But- you know what else you should look at, that's even cooler?
Than that Ralsei plushie? Okay, you shoul look at this server
It's called Craftocracy
Way cooler than whatever that bum *** **** I get on
for this, like, what? I don't even know what this is. 'Kay
This is stupid. 'Kay, but what's not stupid
Is our upcoming Election Season, alright? On the
12th of September, I think?
A'ight?
Any loser, can like, just sign up
and try to run for president, alright?
Even I was president once.
And do I sound fuael- Do I sound qualified for that?
hell no
No.
And... And it happened anyway.
Which is why you should try too. Alright?
Yeah!
We would like to announce that the GREAT system is
already finished and functional in CRSS 3 !
It is completely free and has automatic stops
on every station.
Sometimes they can't keep up with the speed of the minecarts,
but they will slow you down enough that you can manually stop them.
The system currently has five stations, those being
The Evo Station, the Oak Station, the Hagstrom Station,
the Faux Plains station, and the Tilapia Station.
GREAT Staff have said there's plans
to build more stations as other districts,
cities and nations begin to form, and that they will
connect to the main Oak Station in one way or another.
After basic path and tunnel infrastructures were built,
expanding the area of our city southwards,
citizens have already built their own houses and
structures on the new land, which inspired the
town "leaders" to name the area as
"Evo District". GREAT has already seen the
potential this area has, and Line 0 already
includes a station at the Evo District.
BREAKING NEWS!