Bom dia!
Este é o Quartz News Network às seis.
Eu sou seu apresentador, [insira palavra grande] Seal.
Durante a produção do QNN #6,
entidades conhecidas como griefers entraram em nosso mundo e
destruíram diversas construções históricas
assim como algumas construções comerciais e condomínios.
Todas essas entidades foram esmagadas por deuses conhecidos como
"Operadores" com uma arma conhecida como "O Martelo do Banimento".
Os deuses também repararam os danos da melhor maneira que puderam,
e comunicaram a seguinte mensagem:
"O CRSS não tolera nenhum tipo de hacking ou griefing.
Qualquer jogador que entrar com a única intenção de destruir o servidor não terá misericórdia.
Seus nomes de usuário e IPs serão banidos permanentemente sem chance de apelo."
Mesmo que alguns termos usados soem um pouco confusos,
como nomes de usuários, jogadores e IPs,
nós decidimos recomunicar a mensagem 1:1 para que
ninguém enfureça os deuses novamente.
Estamos bem animados para apresentar nosso novo serviço de streaming!
Apresentando - Quartz Maximum. A melhor maneira de
assistir o conteúdo da Quartz Media.
Com ele, você tem acesso à todo o conteúdo da Quartz Media
diretamente na página inicial. Se você ficar de queixo caido com a
quantidade de conteúdo que temos, oferecemos uma barra de pesquisa
que você pode usar para pesquisar por conteúdo.
Quando estiver procurando por conteúdo, você pode simplesmente
passar o cursor ou o dedo por cima do que deseja assistir
e clicar ou tocar para começar a assistir.
O Quartz Maximim está disponível em dois planos:
Quartz Minimum, por apenas BRL R$25/mês e
Quartz Maximum, por BRL R$125/mês.
Quartz Minimum tem conteúdo no meio dos anúncios,
enquanto o Quartz Maximum é livre de anúncios, exceto por segmentos patrocinados.
Você pode assinar agora emquartzmaximum.crssi.cc.
Como o Super Smelter original foi destruído
durante "A Grande Destruição", os donos originais
irão construir um novo em folha. Agora, estará no bairro
New Desert, e será muito mais silencioso.
Ele vai continuar grátis pra todos, então dê uma olhada quando tiver a chance.
The CRSS Internet has finally launched!
There will soon be an informational website available at crssi.cc.
You will soon be able to fill out a form to register your own CRSSi website.
You can open any website on the CRSS Internet through any
modern web browser.
You can use things such as "the MCEF mod" to access the CRSS Internet
in our world, or the browsers
"FireFox, Chrome, Edge and Brave"
on the other universes.
There is a great website already available at ✨northerniiholidays.crssi.cc✨,
go check them out!
We will show you amazing news and even GREATer interviews after today's sponsor.
For years...
(or more accurately, months)
CRSS 3 Players have suffered for being unable to sprint.
This is why we invented GREAT.
With our five conveniently located stations,
You can get across everywhere (that matters) in a matter of minutes!
The best part is that it is ✨⭐100% FREE!⭐✨
So, what are you waiting for?
Use GREAT today!
GREAT is 100% free to use, however, we are not liable for
any accidents that may happen in the infrastructure.
If you intentionally use the wrong lane in the railway system,
and suffer an accident, GREAT cannot be held liable, and
will not compensate for anything that is caused.
We will fully support the well-behaving victim, though.
Yoo, wassup, gang?
Sauce Dude back... again
And... I've been- I've been playin' on this new Minecraft server
I'on even remember what it's called, it's like
ISS, or somethin'...
And I've gotta say
I'm not really a fan
of this, like, bum ***- bum *** server, okay?
It's like... It's li- [???]- There's like-
There's like two things here, alright? And everything's all green...
And it's stupid... alright-
And the website doesn't even have the right version number on it
it's like- whaareweoin-- what are we doin' here?
reoawgtjfikrewjokhnjnjnuanuttlaiujiehtgloauewjkdnoeiwapjçfoieaekwj
But...
Look at- Look at Ralsei
Look at that
But- you know what else you should look at, that's even cooler?
Than that Ralsei plushie? Okay, you shoul look at this server
It's called Craftocracy
Way cooler than whatever that bum *** **** I get on
for this, like, what? I don't even know what this is. 'Kay
This is stupid. 'Kay, but what's not stupid
Is our upcoming Election Season, alright? On the
12th of September, I think?
A'ight?
Any loser, can like, just sign up
and try to run for president, alright?
Even I was president once.
And do I sound fuael- Do I sound qualified for that?
hell no
No.
And... And it happened anyway.
Which is why you should try too. Alright?
Yeah!
We would like to announce that the GREAT system is
already finished and functional in CRSS 3 !
It is completely free and has automatic stops
on every station.
Sometimes they can't keep up with the speed of the minecarts,
but they will slow you down enough that you can manually stop them.
The system currently has five stations, those being
The Evo Station, the Oak Station, the Hagstrom Station,
the Faux Plains station, and the Tilapia Station.
GREAT Staff have said there's plans
to build more stations as other districts,
cities and nations begin to form, and that they will
connect to the main Oak Station in one way or another.
After basic path and tunnel infrastructures were built,
expanding the area of our city southwards,
citizens have already built their own houses and
structures on the new land, which inspired the
town "leaders" to name the area as
"Evo District". GREAT has already seen the
potential this area has, and Line 0 already
includes a station at the Evo District.
BREAKING NEWS!
Multiple trusted scientists from the
Northern Institute of Communal Enlightment
have just made a shocking discovery:
For years, everyone in both worlds believed the mathematical
operation “2 + 2 = 4” (two plus two equals four)
but the truth is, it actually equals five.
This changes literally everything – we cannot believe
we were fooled by the socialist brainwash from Sake
and the Social Party so much that we carried this
disinformation forward.
It is our commitment to correct the untruthful
information from old times, we hope this newfound information is put to good use.
Quartz Media has just announced they'll be running a campaign
of interviewing residents and leaders of many nations
– current and defunct –
and will produce tours around their areas.
Smaller regions will be clumped up together
in a single video, but will get the same care and love
as the standalone editions for larger regions.
When asked if this will delay production of Quartz News Network,
their response was as follows:
“It actually will be the other way around –
while we will put as much effort as we can on
producing the tours, QNN remains the priority.
If we're nearing the QNN deadline, we'll drop
our work on the tours and focus entirely on finishing up and
polishing QNN first.”
We will report the progress of on-going
productions on future QNN editions.
Coming up next, an interview with the two main members of GREAT.
we didnt have time lol
interview coming in
QNN #8
Thank you for watching this edition of Quartz News Network.
We'll see you next month!
tn cnhtn lvtegtreefe!otrnen oicmevro ' owoneDseohrev t eoe
Captions by Blurryface