We entirely forgot to do the PiP News Screens lol
Enjoy the episode without them - they wouldn't really ad much to it.
'meow' - blurry
Good day! This is Quartz News Network at six.
I'm your host,                .
Your.
News.
Hosted by
Thinkseal
Sponsored by
ROP Casino
Made by
Quartz Media LLC
We are not liable for any misinformation shown in this news program.
We are not responsible for your losses in the ROP Casino.
Do not attempt to research alternate results for the equation "2 + 2"
We sincerely ask you to not visit TOA.
#VoteNorthern
We have received official news from the workers of the
Panoramic Metro that it is finally being fixed!
Though progress is being made,
it is important to note that it is not at its GREATest state yet.
New stations are being built, and many plans are being made,
but it will take a while until the project is complete.
While the Panoramic Metro isn't ready, take this moment to walk around ROP
and explore new places you've not been to before!
If you get tired of it, you can always visit the beautiful and
cute country of Chunkia.
Garage programmers from Panorama have created an incredible and
very useful website on the CRSSi!
The group has come up with Yippe!, a company that helps
users find things on the CRSS Internet!
It currently has a public alpha available to be tested, but
they're reportedly working on a more advanced version behind closed doors
so that they can give a more polished experience.
Yippe! has also asked us to remind you to take all cookies
they offer you, because they're yummy and benefit both sides:
They satiate your hunger, and they satiate Yippe!’s costs.
We have just received word that two lovers from far away nations
have come to Panorama to officialise their holy marriage.
Sam, from the same place as Dorothy herself, had decided
with Stella, from a town named after many small rivers,
to officialise their marriage with no big celebrations at the Water Church.
in an interview, they've said they decided to do it more
privately as the first heteroaffective marriage in
the nation would have brought too much attention.
We've been held at bow-point by The Gods to tell you that the
CRSS Internet has received many updates!
The crssi.cc website is still empty,
but other websites – such as Yippe!, GREAT, QNN,
The Minecraft Wiki, and many more – are already available to be accessed.
You can look up any site by searching it on Yippe! Search
through this address: s.yippe.crssi.cc
The Gods have also informed us that, if you want to run your own
CRSSi Website, you should go to crss.cc and click the Discord link.
We are here live at the official residence of the Prime Minister
as they are about to give a press conference.
hai
hai ROP
nyaa
I am here today to announce a new echelon in privacy and safery in ROP
I call it- ViewFinder Pro
It is the best public safety system of all the public safety system
We are also proud to announce we've installed a total of
727 security cameras for 6-7 functions each.
Ever since someone at RUN broke my ladder
I realised that I am - in need of more eyes on our citizens
With this, my assistant Blurry went right to work
Yes. Just look around.
I've installed all the cameras.
Where's my payment?
Now, following this realisation of mine
I've started making some changes.
these should be visible, fingers crossed
we hope these can help improve my peace of mind,
and yours.
So, long story short
Smile, you're on camera :3
nyaaa mrrp meow
Vive Le ROP
Thank you
okay talk done
Coming up after the sponsors:
The GREATest interview you've ever watched.
Thanks for coming to the interview, Pixel!
What are your plans for the expansion of GREAT?
Okay, so, right now,
GREAT is in its funding state.
We have just opened the entirety of Line 0.
A circle line around the, uh, main town
of CRSS 3.
At this moment, we
don't really know where we're gonna expand next.
We are probably gonna go with the demand of our residents
if any of them were active
Um, we are prepared to build more city to build more rail to.
We also have, um, the GREAT Industrial spur
which was built to make it easier to access tree farms,
but, also, other commerce will be added as well.
Um, any comment, Blurry?
m   e   o   w
Thank you.
How much redstone will it cost
to make these new buildings?
Um.
We don't like thinking about cost, in
How much time, how much tears, how much blood, how much pain
did it take to build these,
beautiful rail systems?
Oh. My. God. YES.
The answer is, a [___] lot.
So...
insert laughter track here
The answer is, a [___] lot. Yeah.
We stride to always aim for the lowest costs,
but sadly, there's always some stragglers.
Especially because we're all seeming to have a
mental health crisis at the moment.
Does this answer your question?
Other than the previously mentioned difficulties,
what other difficulties have you encountered while building GREAT?
Okay, so, I think one of the major issues
of designing GREAT, was, um.
building under the house of Ploopy. Uh,
Their house is [___] ginormous.
And, they have a very integrated tunnel system.
So, instead of building through the mountain
as we originally wanted to do, we have instead
to tunnel around it.
We have taxed them for this extra work,
and they are currently in bankruptcy court.
Again, human cost, who gives a [___]?
Okay... Wait- whydoihavan
What are your plans for increasing your revenue
from GREAT to maintain its active growth?
Here at GREAT, we think revenue
is a social construct. We don't think that
we need to make revenue to help provide a GREAT service to our custumers.
The Pixel Regime
Uh, I meant, uh,
The Pixel Administration
hopes to provide public services that don't
require, um, need of payment
from our constituents, because we want to show
that we are able to give without taking.
Except for human lives, but we already went over that.
Does this answer your question?
Yeah.
What are your plans to integrate AI into this product?
Woah, woah, woah, woah! No, don't! Okay?! I- I have a family!
Um, uh, um uh,
You think a hyper-vision super-charged nano-processors of the quantum dimension
we hope to help superstagnate the hypertension of the New Desert river
to help enthusiise our constituents into an AI-hypermind.
What is your response to the allegations of being an economist?
You see
I don't see myself as an economist.
I see myself as a futurist.
I believe that a great country
can be persevered and obtained
if I am the sole power.
I think using the power of the people, to my advantage, we can, build
a GREAT ROP.
Make Panorama Great.
Again?
No, just Great
uh, Make CRSS GREAT              .
[Uh, make CRSS GREAT Railway.]
MAKE CRSS 3 GREAT RAILWAY!
MAKE CR- sorry.
What are your plans to prevent mobs from attacking the riders on GREAT?
Using...
Our AI Hypervision Hivemind Technology
We have built 'GREAT Separation' to prevent mobs
from accessing rails easily.
What is your response to the minecart crash that was seen on the last QNN?
That...
Was-
THAT WAS FAKE NEWS! CRAFTED BY MY COMPETITORS!
TO HELP PROFITEER, PROFITEER THEIR PROPAGANDA!
THEIR PROPAGANDA AGAINST MY CAMPAIGN!
IT'S FAKE NEWS!
DISINFORMATION!
can't believe them...
I AM THE SOURCE OF TRUTH.
IT WAS SAKE! OH, SAKE!
SAKE IS, THE SOURCE OF ALL EVIL!
SAKE, THEY'RE EATING
THEY'RE EATING THE RAILS! THEY'RE EATING-
THEY'RE EATING THE MINECARTS.
Sake... Is eating... The CATS!
the cats- the cats- the cats-
What is your plan for when AI no longer as a buzzword to get free marketing?
Uh, we'll switch to the next buzzword.
We- we- we've ridden... many cases.
I remember back when ROP was doing- I meant,
when CRSS was on the [---] craze.
God, the good old days.
And like, we- we actually had- we-
We were rather involved in the [---] scandal
but we don't like talking about that. Um, so
we did [---] stuff as well.
We- we were actually completely responsible for the [---] crisis.
I'm sorry. Um, and then...
Wait, did I also cause [---]? God, we've done a lot.
And- you know... After we-
sponsored the [---] in [---] we decided that our next thing would be AI.
Um, we also are backing [---] in that [---] as well. Um,
Meow. So, yeah.
Meow.
What is your opinion on💠emoji?
(Diamond Shape With A Dot Inside emoji)
Um. It was pioneered as propaganda
for the Social Party.
It's designed to look like either a [---] hole or a portal cube
depending on your political standpoint.
I see a Portal cube, of course.
Um, I think it should be erradicated.
Have you checked if the exits are locked to this building?
Um. I really don't care. That's Blurry's problem.
I- I'm just- I'm here. You know? I'm paid a salary,
Like, I could not give a [---]. I barely eve-
I just work here. And I have absolutely no other involvement
with this organisation other than being brought on to interviews,
and sometimes making music. You know, like
some people think that just because I'm part of QNN,
it means I'm a journalist. (I'm secretely [---] but don't tell people)
And like, they are completely wrong, like
I just work here. There is nothing else.
No other involvement with QNN.
But are you not the prime minister?
I don't wish to comment on that.
Wait, how did I become the prime min-
What is your response to the trademark infringement on your name of pixels on screens?
Um. Okay, so- I've had...
Several interviews with Yippe!.
Most of them job interviews. Um.
I failed all of them.
Um.
Anyway, I like to think we can coexist.
Even though, we are both equally as important,
I have the upper hand, because I make music,
and Yippe!, doesn't.
What is your- What is your plan to make sure that GREAT will last forever and never degrade?
Okay, so, essentially: Totaliarism... nism.
By consolidating business and the state into one megapower,
we are able to take advantage of AI-Supercharged
Rail Mending
so that we can fire Blurry, and it can maintain itself.
What the [---]???
What did I do???
Uh, you will die someday.
There's no issues with that logic!
How long will it take until great is Touring Complete?
Uh, GREAT is actually already touring complete.
Thanks to its Advanced AI Integration,
we've partnered with ClosedGB to provide the best
experience to our customers, and now
the experience can be passed on to you!
Using GREAT+, USD $5/month or CAD $6/month,
you can experience the best of GREAT's amazing AI features!
For the price, of a car.
Sounds quite nice, right?
What is your plans to bring GREAT to the 4th dimension
to be able to traverse space and time at the same time?
So, actually, we've already introduced this feature to our GREAT+ plan!
If you just go, and enable the '4th dimension' option
Um, it's in settings, in privacy. Uh, It also enables data tracking...
Don't think about it too hard.
It will let you traverse the 4th and the 5th dimensions
Uh, so that you can play the best versions of Hyper Chess.
Uh, I meant, uh
Railway. This also lets you teleport to the main CRSS realm,
where GREAT does not exist, but you can take the Metro.
That's good enough, right? H1?
Going back a little bit,
How am I the prime minister of this place too??
Um. I don't know.
Huh, I guess I just feel like leader.
What is your response to apparently being my dog,
and having apparently the same cat as me?
I'm just such a cutie. Meow.
Um...
Next question.
What an amazing interview!
What an amazing interview this has been!
Yes.
Back to your regularly scheduled QNN.
meow
send hel