philososeal انا مضيفكم .Quartz Network News
(QNN) at 6 طاب يومكم. معكم
[مقدمت الاخبار العاجلة]
[موسيقى]
Your.
News.
ROP Casino برعايت
Quartz Media LTD من انتاج
We are not liable for any misinformation shown in this news program
We are not responsible for your losses in the ROP Casino.
We sincerely ask you to not visit TOA
Do not look directly at the operational end of the device.
First up tonight- an odd grass was spotted
by Blurry near the new desert today.
It’s purple in colour, and nearby residents
are very worried for their safety.
It is currently in laboratory testing,
and results are still pending.
Breaking news - a wave of immature behaviour
has struck Panorama, leaving locals shocked.
We spoke with a local
resident, Blurry, for insight.
— Blurry, what has gotten the
people of Panorama so shocked?
— People keep making unhinged
and immature jokes about
stuff that can't be said here or
we'll get banned.
— What do you think should be
done about these immature jokes?
— ...Burn the city down.
— Okay!
Do you love your family and
produce your own farm food?
Is your farm food full of
annoying and dangerous pests??
Introducing instant Harming Potions in Minecraft (iHPM)!
The world’s #1 Pesticide!
You can hire us to throw these at your
farm, and your crops will be intact!
Now you can go back to being happy with
your family with your self-made food!
DISCLAIMER: [Really, REALLY long
list of fictional side-effects]
Ever since our gratuitous and noble leader
WorldWidePixel freed the people of
Panorama from the clutches of Sake
we have had open borders with the
historical and beautiful country of Chunkia.
Many Panoramic tourists have loved
the scenic views and cute buildings.
Explorers have found a barrel full of
illegal Bedrock near one of the End Portals.
We have somehow gotten this
information before the authorities,
so we’re going to be responsible about it
and leave the coordinates here so
they can deal with it, and not us!
Scientists have dug to the “center” of the world,
and have discovered that it just ends,
and it’s just flat!
None of the scientists have
survived this journey though,
as they fell to infinity and beyond
in something they called “The Void”.
We only have access to this information as
they were making a livestream when it happened.
And, as of today, the livestream is miraculously
still online. Here’s what it currently looks like.
[GLITCHING LIVESTREAM]
[PLACEHOLDER QNN INTRO]
[BURNING REPUBLIC OF PANORAMA]
[GLITCHING LIVESTREAM]
[OLD YOUTUBE THUMBNAIL
OF ALPHA MINECRAFT]
[GLITCHING LIVESTREAM]
[PERSON NEAR FLAG IN
A PIXEL ART IN CLASSIC MINECRAFT]
[GLITCHING LIVESTREAM]
[GARBLED MAC SCREEN]
[THE FIRST HEROBRINE
SCREENSHOT, FLASHING]
[CREDITS SEQUENCE]
[MUSIC]