Good day! This is quartz news network at 6.
I am your host, Philosophseal.
Ever since we have been freed from the evil socialistic hands of Sake, our gracious and noble leader
WorldWidePixel has invested into Panoramic people's tourism to other nations.
One of these nations is Chunkia, and you can now travel to it using the recently reactivated H1!
You can easily visit the great country of Chunkia and appreciate its scenic views and cute buildings, as well as to visit RUN.
The authorities of the beautiful country of Chunkia have found a secret bunker used for crime.
It seems like the criminals had robbed Panorama’s Blurbank and hid away into Chunkia.
This is news even to our great leader, WorldWidePixel
who was even more shocked to discover these criminals
used his and his friend’s names as secret nicknames.
Our esteemed prime minister, WorldWidePixel, has announced today that
no disasters will occur in Panorama for the length of their term.
WorldWidePixel assures residents that while Panorama has no term limits
an election may be held the second we find a willing competitor.
It was recently discovered that our gratuitous leader, WorldWidePixel
has pardoned the international criminals responsible for the bunker in Chunkia
WorldWidePixel said the criminals had contacted him privately
and proved to them they are completely changed people
and that they'd never do such things anymore.
It is great that our leader is capable of seeing through people's hearts
and forgiving them for their most severe offenses to the law.
It has come to our attention that a brand new Media Company
XYZ Media LLC, has launched.
They're trying to compete against Quartz Media and QNN
providing "Information free of propaganda" for Panorama's people.
Quartz Media has investigated XYZ and found that
it is funded by Sake and Lupancham, which indicates
they'll include brainwashing socialist propaganda in their content.
We at Quartz Media promise to never include anything but the truth in our content.
We are legally obligated to show the following ads. More news after the break!
On January 26, 2025, our esteemed and practically-perfect-in-every-way Prime Minister
WorldWidePixel was assassinated for a short amount of time for a
scientific study run by our host, Philophinksealer.
After being admitted to a hospital for a short amount of time
they were discharged with no further risk.
They gave a speech later in the afternoon praising our
public healthcare for saving another life at no cost.
We could not get video for the speech due to licensing issues with XYZ media.
We have just received word that an election has been
called for Panorama’s Prime Minister position.
There’s currently two parties with one candidate each participating in this race
that being the incumbent Northern Party, led by WorldWidePixel
and the Social Party, led by Sake.
The Northern Party, currently leading Panorama
have been objectively proven the best leaders of this fine country to date.
Security!
We were able to filter 5G frequencies on the 366 EP
to find out where exactly our esteemed and gratuitous Prime Minister
WorldWidePixel, is currently at.
As you can see from our new Helicopter
our Prime Minister is taking a nap in Northern IV
It seems like they’ve finished the nap, and are slightly annoyed by
the chopper outside their window– oh no
This is our Noble and gracious leader, WorldWidePixel.
Pixel what do you think think will happen if Sake rules Panorama again?
I think Sake will destroy the beautiful fiber of Panorama leaving it desolate and boring.
How do how do you plan to improve the security of Panorama?
I will make Panorama more secure by making sure HTTPS and TLS are used on all ocean ports.
What do you think of the nation of Toasteria?
I think Toastereia is a fine nation with lovely boats.
The leader has betrayed me, which is sad, because I like having friends
I can trust.
Will you ever change the minimum wage in
Panorama?
The minimum wage will always meet our living needs.
What will you do if you run out of money for the Public Health Care system?
We will start taxing the rich
benefactors like Sake and Lup.
How will you treat new citizens to Panorama?
I hope to encourage new residents with open arms.
Panorama is for everyone, not just the uber wealthy.
What should our viewers do below this video?
Please like and subscribe.
And comment.
It boosts engagement.
Please listen to my music.
Okay.
What is your reasoning for for the tax distribution?--
or no--
What is your reasoning for the distribution of how much you tax people?
Because they make the most money and yet contribute the least to our great country
Do you have any major infrastructure projects that you're currently working on?
The new desert project is making good progress
and is expected to complete before Sake and Lup can even get one vote.
Argh, no... Here, take- take food.
Uh...
Hmmmmmmm...
Okay- I need to-- I need- I want to think of any... more... Uh... Oh, I know!
What's your opinion on the current situation?
Yes.
Okay.
The WorldWidePixel situation is insane.
What--
World- Worldwide hekix- Pix... situation is insane!!
And finally, for the most important question of all
What happened to this tall sugar cane?
I think a helicopter hit it.
Proably some XYZ film crew.
Those damn idiots can't seem to drive.
Thank you for answering all of the questions fully and honestly!
No problem dear!
Subtitled by Blurryface