Good day!
This is Quartz News Network at 6.
I'm your host AI-Seal
Breaking News
Citizens of Panorama have alerted us about an alarming infestation of chicken jockeys in Panorama.
These creatures seem to have suddenly excessively appeared after Back Jlack came to visit us.
Please be aware that these creatures are very dangerous
and do not like human company.
Our film crew had to use immense zoom to capture images
of them.
Breaking News
Our competitor,
XYZ Media LLC
still hasn't built a studio for recording their news program.
This is even more surprising considering they're the alleged
culprits of breaking the tall sugar cane
Breaking News
The writers of CRSS content have gone on strike
due to struggling with creativity, time, and general mental health.
This might just be the first actually mostly serious QNN News Rreport
and it may also just explain why May might not have a QNN episode and also explains why this edition is so tiny.
We hope the next edition will be... Anything but this.
Thanks for watching, see you next time.