Good day!
This is Quartz News Network at 6.
I'm your host, ThoughtSeal.
Our gratuitous Prime Minister has announced
that they,
through a mysterious source named BlueSky,
have found an event named BlanketCon '25.
It's happening during the next month.
It seems to be a convention about mods,
which seems to mean things imported from the world of every author in the convention.
Some of these mods are:
Snapper,
a tool that makes sorting pictures easier.
Hollow,
blocks and entities inspired by Hollow
Ambitions from someone called Mojang.
Joy,
bed sheets, candles, and entities with LGBT tweaks.
Sentient Pants...
Apparently we have ThinkPant now.
It appears The Incredible Poloopy504 has reappeared
in CRSS and fixed the windmill at their Farm.
In an interview, they've told us that they came back
to help Rhys
gather information about their house and since they were back they decided to fix the windmill too.
Blurry met up with them and helped with the resources he had available.
He also gifted them in elytra and fireworks,
as the last time Ploopy were seen was way before those
were around.
Private reporters have contacted us about the apparent firing of the QNN host, ThinkSeal.
We would like to inform our audience that ThinkSeal is still alive and well,
as he has not been hurt or injured in any way.
Have you ever wanted to make your game look like Bad Apple?
No?
Well,
now you can anyways with the Bad Apple Shaders!
It will turn your game into something completely different
where the world is black and the entities are right, or
the exact opposite.
In addition to all of this, with the latest update
we also now have translucency, transparency, and much more supported.
Download Bad Apple Shaders today at badapple.blurry.gay
We have found the alleged culprits of breaking
the tall sugar cane in Panorama.
The XYZ film crew has been taken to court
by Quartz Industries Inc. for allegedly destroying
the oldest and biggest plant in the world.
We were testing the new auto-pilot feature in our helicopter
and went to try to fly over the Known Nation Limits.
This led us to discover the new continent of trench.
It has a single City on it, Dema
but something quite weird happens when we try to get footage of it.
The continent of trench is over 14,000 meters away from
Toasteria, completely decimating their northernmost status.
We have discovered that the Romanian Federation of Minecraft Leader is extremely poor.
They barely have any diamonds and not even an elytra!
This raises the questions:
Is it even safe to live in RFM?
Can the leader even provide me actual safety?
Does this mean my silliness truly cannot be contained?!
We advise you stay in Panorama as we already don't contain your silliness.
We know what is best for our people,
and you should not worry.
.msilatipaC .msilaicoS .nrehtroN etoV
This has been Quartz News Network. Thank you for watching, and see you next month!